There are worse things than dying.
Dead Birds is a horror, thriller, western film directed by Alex Turner.
Towards the end of the Civil War, a group of Confederate soldiers hole up on an abandoned
plantation after robbing a bank, and find themselves at the mercy of supernatural forces.
William, played by Henry Thomas.
Sam, played by Patrick Fugit.
Clyde, played by Michael Shannon.
Annabelle, played by Nicki Aycox.
Todd, played by Isaiah Washington.
Joseph, played by Mark Boone Junior.
Dead Birds is a 2004 American Western horror film directed by Alex Turner, and starring Henry
Thomas, Nicki Aycox, Isaiah Washington, Patrick Fugit, and Michael Shannon.
The film centers on a group of deserters turned bank robbers who come face-to-face with
supernatural forces while hiding in an abandoned plantation after robbing a bank.
The film was given a limited re-release on February 5, 2010, at the NuArt
Theatre in Los Angeles; and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of bank, desertion, alabama, supernatural, plantation.
The tone is dark and intense.